gooten.com 2016-12-23

# Gooten

Welcome to Gooten (“Gooten”, “we”, “us” and “our”). Gooten provides digital innovation and the power of making design and technology connect. When you use the Platform as defined in our [Terms of Service](https://www.gooten.com/terms/) you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy also explains the treatment of information provided or collected through the Platform that we make available on third-party sites or platforms if disclosed to you in connection with your use of the Platform.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications ("Third Party Services") that you elect to access through the Platform or to individuals that we don't manage or employ. While we try to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we don't take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of all Third Party Services you access through the Platform.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [hello@gooten.com](mailto:hello@gooten.com).

#### 1.Information Collection and Use

We collect and use your information to (i) provide and measure use of the Platform and improve it over time, (ii) communicate with you about your user account or transactions with us, (iii) send you information about changes to Platform features or our policies, (iv) send you offers and promotions, (v) personalize content for you on the Platform, (vi) detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or applicable law, and (vii) as further described in this Privacy Policy.

#### 2.Information Collected Upon Registration

To use the Platform, you will need to create a user account with us. When you create or reconfigure a user account with us, you are required to provide us with the following information: first name, surname, company name, e-mail address, website address, user name, password, mailing address and telephone number (collectively, “User Information”). Also, financial details such as your bank account number and/or credit card number will be collected by us and processed if you make a purchase through the Platform (collectively, “Financial Information,” and together with Registration Information, “Registration Information”). We may store this information so that it can be used for the purposes explained in this Privacy Policy.

#### 3.Additional Information Collected Through Use of the Platform

You may provide us with additional information in connection with your use of the Platform, including: (i) transaction information you provide when you request information or use the Platform, (ii) location information when you visit and use the Platform, including location information either provided by a mobile device interacting with the Platform, or associated with your IP address, where we are permitted by applicable law to process this information, and (iii) usage, viewing and technical data when you visit and use the Platform or open e-mails and other communications we send to you.

We may use your contact information to send you information about the Platform or to advertise and market to you] . You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or by making changes to your account settings.

Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Platform. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with our website, applications and advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

#### 4.Communications

We may use your contact information to send you information about the Platform or to advertise and market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or by making changes to your account settings.

If you e-mail us, we may keep your message, e-mail address and contact information to respond to your request.

#### 5.Log Data

Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Platform. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with our website, applications and advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

#### 6.Links to Third Party Websites

The Platform may contain links to other websites. We may keep track of how you interact with links across the Platform including Third Party Services by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve the Platform and as part of our business, including advertising and marketing, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on or shared with others.

We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other websites to which we provide links from the Platform. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the website sponsor when linking to other websites.

#### 7.Cookies

Like many websites and mobile applications, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Platform. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Platform, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Platform, and to improve the Platform. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

#### 8.Third Party Services

We use a variety of Third Party Services hosted by unaffiliated third parties to help provide the Platform, and to help us understand the use thereof. These Third Party Services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We require these companies to use your information only to provide the particular function and/or service and do not authorize them to use your information for any other reason.

#### 9.Law and Harm

We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect our rights or property.

#### 10.Data Security and Integrity

The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your personal information. However, there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically. The personal information we collect is stored within databases that we control. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect your information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

#### 11.Business Transfers

In the event that Breakout Commerce, Inc. d/b/a Gooten is directly or indirectly involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, information that we have collected may be transferred as part of that transaction. We will use reasonable efforts to ensure this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity, but we cannot assure you that, upon completion of any such transfer, the new entity will maintain this Privacy Policy in its current form.

#### 12.Modifying Your Personal Information

We provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provide to us and associated with your account. See your account settings for details. Please be aware that, if you do not allow us to collect personal information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain aspects of the Platform to you, and we may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences.

You can also permanently deactivate your account at any time. See your account settings for details. Once your account has been deactivated, it may not be possible to restore your account, even if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated.

#### 13.Our Policy Towards Children

The Platform is not directed to children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at hello@gooten.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. If you become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [hello@gooten.com](mailto:hello@gooten.com).

#### 14.Changes to this Policy

Gooten may modify or update this Policy at any time without notice and at our sole discretion. Any additional or different terms in this Policy will be effective upon being posted on or in connection with the Platform. It is your responsibility to review this Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Platform following the posting of any additional or different terms in this Policy constitutes your irrevocable acceptance of those additional or different terms. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE PLATFORM.

© 2015 Breakout Commerce, Inc. d/b/a Gooten.
